(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-06-24T00:24:03.626339",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
全世界、激震！
The entire world is shaken!
あの超大作が
That blockbuster movie...
ついに
Is finally...
スクリーンへ！！
Coming to the screen!!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
Humanity's hope...
4人の「■■■■」に託された
Has been entrusted to four [censored].
なんだ？ここは！？
What? What is this place?!
どうして……こんなのひどいよー！
Why...? This is so cruel!
私のことはもういい！先に行け！
Don't worry about me! Go on ahead!
いろは～～～～！！！！
Iroha~~~~!!!!
おい、ふざけんな！
Hey, stop messing around!
何で？
Why?
私たちの絆は永遠！
Our bond is eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
Let's all save humanity!!
絶対に忘れないよ……
I will never forget you...
自分史上、最高傑作です
It's the greatest masterpiece of my life.
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は……この中にいる！
The culprit... is among us!
えー！？
What?!
「なんかすごいミステリー」約1位
Ranked roughly #1 in 'Somehow Amazing Mysteries'
きゃーーーー
Kyaaaaa!
これは……
This is...
謎が謎を呼ぶ怒涛の展開
A turbulent progression where mystery leads to mystery
背後から刀で一振り……
A single slash with a sword from behind...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Master Detective, what is the matter?
怪しい
Suspicious.
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！
As if I can stay in the same place as a murderer!
部屋に戻らせてもらう！
I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious.
……ふふふふふ
...Fufufufufu.
怪しい
Suspicious.
登場人物全員”容疑者”
Every character is a 'suspect'
最初から最後までハラハラドキドキでした
I was on the edge of my seat from start to finish.
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
My name is Hakui Koyori! An ordinary high school student you can find anywhere!
ただ一つ人と違うことは、科学が好き……ってところかな？
The only thing that sets me apart is... I guess that I love science?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ーー
Oh no! I'm late, I'm late!
きゃー！
Kyaa!
いったー！
Ouch!
転校初日から始まる ドタバタな日常！？
A hectic daily life starting from the first day of transferring!?
見つけた
Found you.
一緒にいると、なんか安心するでござる！
When we are together, I feel somehow relieved!
いただきましよー！
I'll be taking this!
うわ、おもしれー女
Whoa, what an interesting woman.
個性あふれる4人が紡ぐ 甘じょっぱい四角な物語――
A bittersweet quadrangle story woven by four unique individuals—
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The bittersweetness was exquisite!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた……！ holoX4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！
A-Are you...! Did you search for 'holoX 4th Anniversary'?!
決して、検索してはイケナイ……
Never search for it...
holoX 4周年
holoX 4th Anniversary
"SSholoX4周年"を検索した人間に降りかかる数々の出来事――
The numerous events that befall those who search 'SSholoX 4th Anniversary'...
ルイ姉…
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから
Iroha, it's okay.
いろは？
Iroha?
いろは！
Iroha!
どぅわぁー！
Whoa!
（すごい悲鳴！）
[Amazing scream!]
終始、鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー！
I had goosebumps the whole time!
せーの！ holoX4周年サイコー！
Ready, go! holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
ラララパタ パララパタ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-la-pa-ta...
ラララパタ パララパタパ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-la-pa-ta-pa...
ラララパタ パララパタ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-la-pa-ta...
ラララパタ パラパタパラパタパ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-pa-ta-pa-la-pa-ta-pa...
迷宮なラビリンス
Labyrinthine Labyrinth
舞い込んできた招待状
An invitation that fluttered in
秘密で秘匿の異次元マンション
A secret and hidden alternative dimension mansion
ガタガタと鳴るあの扉に
That rattling door...
NO WAY! 逃げ道
NO WAY! Escape route...
あっち！
Over there!
迫る箱庭ウォークライ保存
The war cry of the approaching miniature garden
交差路に突破口は
At the intersection, is there a breakthrough...
堂々巡りの走馬灯
A carousel of memories going in circles
エクスに吸い込まれてゆく
Being sucked into the Ex
各員、敵ござれ！
Everyone, enemies ahead!
有象無象のディメンション
Dimension of the rabble
ドアが開くとライバル登場
When the door opens, a rival appears
さあ交わすご陽気なフィーバー
Now, let's exchange a cheerful fever
響け
Echoing...
笑い声
Laughter!
ラララパタ パララパタ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-la-pa-ta...
ラララパタ パラパタパラパタパ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-pa-ta-pa-la-pa-ta-pa...
絡まり合って
Entangling with each other,
解き放って
releasing...
ここからこそ始まる
From here, it truly begins,
素敵な迷宮なラビリンス保存
a wonderful labyrinthine labyrinth.
廻りだす真実
The spinning truth,
狂いだす現実
the reality going mad,
ねじれだす次元
the twisting dimension,
戻れない道
the road with no return.
今日不意に接続Wi-Fi
Today, suddenly connected Wi-Fi
この街で最強ルームだけど
It's the strongest room in this city, but...
カタカタの回廊は普通にアブノーマル
The rattling corridor is normally abnormal.
ワンショット
One shot...
ヴァンパイア
Vampire!
真実踊るマリオネット
A marionette dancing the truth,
落ちる部屋はダンスメイト
the falling room is a dance mate.
バグり合いは眼中にないが 悪魔はあかんくない？
Clashing over bugs is not in my sights, but isn't the devil bad?
エクスに吸い込まれてゆく
Being sucked into the Ex...
迷える子羊君たち！
Wandering lambs!
お砂糖、スパイス、それとピンクな4周年で！
Sugar, spice, and a pink 4th anniversary!
ハイになれるドリンクできたよ！
I made a drink that can make you high!
毒々飲んでくださいね
Please drink poisonously.
holoXを餌食に…ははは！
holoX as prey... hahaha!
さあさあ、皆の者、飲んでいこうでござる！
Now now, everyone, let's drink!
我が世の…って、いやお前が飲むんかい！
My world... wait, why are you the one drinking?!
じゃあ、とりあえず…
Then, for now...
乾杯！
Cheers!
関わりの回路はカラー保存
The circuit of involvement is color,
底抜けの冷笑系アプローチ保存
a bottomless cynical approach.
塗り替えられる日常保存
The daily life being repainted,
響き渡る笑い声保存
the echoing laughter.
お前たちもな！
You guys too!
ラララパタ パララパタ
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-la-pa-ta...
ラララパタ パララパタ保存
ラララパタ パラパタパラパタパ保存
La-la-la-pa-ta, pa-la-pa-ta-pa-la-pa-ta-pa!
立ち上がれ 手に持つもの
Stand up! What you hold in your hands...
重ねて 声を高らかに
...put them together and raise your voices high!
らぱぱ たら らぱぱ
Lapapa, tara rapapa...
冷徹の 海を超えるため
...to cross the freezing sea!
つまり本気！
In other words, we're serious!
普通が嫌い
We hate being ordinary!
生きるのって
Living our lives...
そんなに甘くない
...isn't that easy!
スーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
Super Future Party Labyrinth!
ファイブ！
Five!
ハァーーイ！ イェーーイ！
Haaay! Yeaah!
ということで！
And with that...
ホロックス ４周年ーー！
...holoX's 4th anniversary!
おめでとうー！ ありがとうー！
Congratulations! Thank you!
おめでとうおめでとう！ ありがとうありがとう！
Congrats, congrats! Thank you, thank you!
４周年だ！
It's our 4th anniversary!
張り切っていくぞー！ おーー！
Let's give it our all! Yeah!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を...
So, let's share our ambitions for our future activities...
早いね展開！ 早いね！
That's a quick transition! So fast!
どうする？私から？
What should we do? Me first?
私から？ 聞いてないよー！
Me? I didn't hear about this!
どうしようかな... えー、えーっと...
What should I do... Um, err...
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
えーっと、どうしようかな... えー...
Err, what should I do... Um...
5年目も 頑張るぞ！ホロックス頑張るぞー！
In our 5th year too, I'll do my best! holoX will do our best!
おー！ 頑張るぞー！ ありがとう！
Oh! Let's do our best! Thank you!
はい、じゃあお次！
Alright, next up!
はい！えー、この5年目は
Yes! In this 5th year...
4人でもっと団結力をグッと...グッとさせて！
...the four of us will make our solidarity even tighter!
そろそろ、日本征服くらいはしていきたいなと！
We want to conquer Japan pretty soon!
日本征服！ 5年目のね
Conquering Japan! In our 5th year...
きりのいいところでね
...at this great milestone.
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど
The world might be a bit difficult still...
日本征服頑張ります！
...but we'll do our best to conquer Japan!
イェーイ！ 頑張ろう！
Yeah! Let's do it!
はい、風真！
Okay, Kazama!
はい！皆さん、ごー！
Yes! Everyone, go...!
ご？ ござるの、ごー！
Go? The 'go' in 'gozaru'!
ということで5年目もね、元気に健やかに
So, in our 5th year too, healthily, happily...
健康に活動頑張っていきたいと思います！
...and soundly, we want to do our best in our activities!
ホロックス、5周年...あ、5年目頑張ろう！
holoX, 5th anniversary... ah, let's do our best in our 5th year!
5周年まで頑張ろう！ 頑張ろう頑張ろう！
Let's do our best until our 5th anniversary! Let's do it!
5周年まで頑張るぞ！ おー！
We'll do our best until our 5th anniversary! Yeah!
じゃあ私いいですか？
Okay, is it my turn?
今年も、生き残るぞーー！
This year too, we will survive!
生き残ることを言ってるよね
You're talking about surviving again.
でも生き残れた、今年も！ 生き残れた！
But we survived this year too! We survived!
そして、来年こそ！
And next year!
5年目こそ！
In our 5th year too!
我々の年にするぞーー！
We will make it our year!
おーー！
Yeah!
ちょっとださい、ポーズがださい...
That's a bit lame, your pose is lame...
なんでなんで？みんなと同じのだよ！
Why, why? It's the same as everyone else's!
え？みんな同じ...
Huh? Everyone's is the same...
こよりと風真のダサさはどうでもいいとして
Well, never mind Koyori and Kazama's lameness...
おい！
Hey!
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Everyone, please take a look at this!
ライブステージ！
This live stage!
すごーい！ めっちゃカッコよくない？
Amazing! Isn't it so cool?
ホロックスの最初の登場からうちらカッコよかったよね
We were so cool right from holoX's first entrance, weren't we?
カッコよかった！ カッコよかったよ！
We were! We were indeed cool!
待って、ホロックスのマークに助けられちゃったからね
Wait, we were saved by the holoX logo, you know!
カッコよかったよね！
We did look cool!
しかも、このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて
Moreover, this stage isn't just wide...
色々な仕掛けがありますので！
...there are all kinds of gimmicks!
何だって？
What's that?
大注目して、何か出てきたりとか...
Keep your eyes peeled, maybe something will pop up...
出てきたり？ 出てきたりとか？
Pop up? Something popping up?
耳生える？ 耳はもう生えてる！
Ears growing? Ears are already grown!
あと、上がったりとか...
And going up...
上がったり？ 尻尾が上がってんだよ！
Going up? My tail is already up!
変形したりとかさ
Or transforming...
合体とか！
...or combining!
合体？ いや、さすがに無理だろ
Combining? No, surely that's impossible.
合体したい！ 合体したい！
I want to combine! Let's combine!
できますか？こよりさん
Can you do it, Koyori-san?
合体はやりたかったんですけど...
I wanted to do a combination...
こよりもそういうの大好きなんだけど...
...and I love that kind of stuff too...
ちょっとさすがに、ホロックス、予算が少なく...
...but honestly, holoX's budget is a bit low...
当たり前じゃないですか！ いくらかけてると思ってるの！
Well, of course it is! How much do you think we spent on this?!
私たちの給料をね、ねだってもいいよね
We can ask for a salary raise, right?
でも、このステージできたからいいじゃん！
But we got this stage, so it's fine!
ありがとう、こより！ ありがとう！
Thank you, Koyori! Thank you!
ということで、5年目もホロックスを、皆さん、ぜひ
So, in our 5th year too, everyone, please...
こんな...
...even though we're...
こんな我々ですけど、よろしくお願いします！
...like this, please support us!
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
ここで、お知らせでございます！
And now, we have an announcement!
お知らせだ！ お知らせだよ！
An announcement! It's an announcement!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると
If you join the Hololive official channel membership...
なんと！限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので
...you can use limited emoji stamps!
ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
Please use them in the comments to liven things up!
さらに！今日からもう一つメンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども
Furthermore, there is another membership perk starting today...
なんと、新曲『スキ魔バスター』と『プライベートアイズ』の壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
...you can also get wallpapers for the new songs 'Sukima Buster' and 'Private Eyes'!
欲しい！ 私たちが欲しい！
I want them! We want them ourselves!
私たちも入らなきゃいけないのかな？
Do we have to join the membership too?
もらえるもらえる！
We can get them!
おめでとうございまーす！ / はい！
Congratulations! / Yes!
そして、本日は何やらライブだけではなく？
And today, it seems there's not just a live performance?
お？重要な？
Oh? Important...?
情報がもりもりもりもり盛りだくさんらしいので！
...information is piled up high!
もりもり盛りだくさん！
Lots and lots of info!
皆さん、最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
Everyone, make sure you watch until the very end!
途中退出禁止です！よろしくお願いします！
Leaving halfway is forbidden! Please treat us well!
もりもりもり...森の字を作る
Mori, mori... Let's make the kanji for forest (森)!
三人で？三人で森を作る？
The three of us? The three of us make a forest?
混ぜるな！混ぜるな！
Don't mix us in! Don't mix us in!
ちょっと待ってください！何ですか何ですか？早くしないと！
Wait a minute! What is this, what is this? We have to hurry!
みんなに見せらんないから、ライブ！
Or we won't be able to show everyone the live show!
そうそう！早速...
Yes, yes! Right away...
最初は...ドゥルドゥルドゥルドゥル...
First up is... *drumroll*...
こよちゃんのパートから！
Koyori-chan's part!
イェーイ！
Yay!
何だそのポーズ！ / 可愛いでしょ！
What is that pose?! / Isn't it cute?!
ちょっと、ちょっと...可愛い！
Wait, wait... It's cute!
いってらっしゃーい！
Have a good show!
頑張ってね！バイバーイ！
Do your best! Bye-bye!
見てるよー！走って！そこ広いから！
We're watching! Run! It's wide over there!
急かさないで！ / 邪魔だから行くよ
Don't rush me! / You're in the way, so I'm going.
え？俺たちも？ / 早く早く！早くして！
What? Us too? / Hurry, hurry! Hurry up!
行くぜ！行くぜ！早く！
Let's go! Let's go! Hurry!
爆ラブ+ケミストリー
作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
[Title: Baku-Love + Chemistry
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Nayutalien]
ラブは気化センセーション 存在自体マジ勘違い
Love is a vaporization sensation! The existence itself is a total misunderstanding!
調合は未完成 トキメキのケミカル
The concoction is incomplete, heart-throbbing chemicals!
え、なるほど？そんじゃこれならどうだかと
Eh, I see? Well then, how about this?
オキシトシン ドーパミン セロトニン
Oxytocin, dopamine, serotonin!
あわだつこのこの感情
This bubbling emotion...
混ぜるほどにはまる はまる
The more it mixes, the more I get hooked, hooked!
上昇のモーション
Rising motion!
奇跡的に愛しくなれ
Miraculously become lovely!
フラスコにハート やべ、なにかあった
A heart in a flask! Uh oh, something happened!
効果のてすと 君が1番！
Testing the effect, you are number one!
ほら ぼう ぼう ぼう 君に熱
Look, burning, burning, burning, fever for you!
ちょっと危険なまぜまぜ
A slightly dangerous mix-mix!
どっかーん！ケミストリーだ！
Ka-boom! It's chemistry!
あいまいな君とのプラトニック・ラブに
In a platonic love with the ambiguous you,
平和っぽい恋のジェネリック
A generic, peaceful love.
もっと夢中になりたいな
I want to get more obsessed with you!
急接近したい君の胸
I want to get rapidly close to your chest,
その前にシンクロプラクティス
Before that, a synchro practice!
爆ラブ君とケミストリー
Baku-Love chemistry with you!
今度はもっと甘い液
This time, an even sweeter liquid!
解けるくらいドキドキするはず
It should make your heart throb enough to melt!
え、白い煙？はい、出たー！
Eh, white smoke? Yes, here it comes!
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない！
That's not the "heart-throbbing" type!
けど、まあある意味成功かな？
But, well, in a way, is it a success?
ラブは急展開 一秒待てない時間保存
Love develops suddenly! A time that can't wait even a second!
調合は必殺 判定はどうでしょう？
The concoction is a deadly blow! How is the judgment?
え、どうして！？
Eh, why!?
想定外の爆発を君と重ねてく 化学変化で
Overlapping unexpected explosions with you, through chemical change!
きゅっと冷まさせて二人のマージ
Cooling down to merge the two of us!
ラブのデシベル 君が一番！
Decibel of love, you are number one!
ほら ぼう ぼう ぼう 君に熱
Look, burning, burning, burning, fever for you!
僕が君のアンチドート
I am your antidote!
どっかーん！ケミストリーだ！
Ka-boom! It's chemistry!
あいまいな君とのプラトニック・ラブに
In a platonic love with the ambiguous you,
平和っぽい恋 of ジェネリック
A generic, peaceful love.
どんな毒も加速して
Accelerating any poison...
どっかーん！
Ka-boom!
君プラスハート 解け合ってまぜまぜシナジー
You plus heart! Melting and mixing synergy!
君こそが愛のアトミック
You are the atomic force of love!
もっと夢中になりたいな
I want to get more obsessed with you!
急接近したい君の胸保存
I want to get rapidly close to your chest,
その前にシンクロプラクティス
Before that, a synchro practice!
爆ラブ君と追検証！
Baku-Love re-verification with you!
きゅんとして僕の胸
My chest tightening with love...
その前にシンクロプラクティス
Before that, a synchro practice!
爆ラブ君とケミストリー 実験は君と永遠なり！
Baku-Love chemistry with you! The experiment with you is forever!
Overtime
作詞・作曲・編曲：jon-YAKITORY
[Title: Overtime
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: jon-YAKITORY]
君が好きってこの感情に潰されてる
I'm being crushed by this feeling of liking you.
足りないのはどちらの方かどうでもいいかも
Which of us is lacking, maybe it doesn't matter.
傷ついたって知らないよね 責任の所在
You don't care if I get hurt, where does the responsibility lie?
私は何で好きなんだって問い出す性で
With my nature of questioning why I love you,
最低だなって思ったあの子の方が良いんだもんね
since that girl I thought was the worst is better, right?
私興味ないよ君なんて
I have no interest in you at all.
中途半端な容れ物(イレ)で舐めた真似
Making light of me with such a half-hearted vessel.
傲慢で稀重なこの愛に
By this arrogant and precious love,
壊されないで愛
don't let love be destroyed.
剥がされないで愛
Don't let love be torn away.
止めどないよ君の愛を独り占めしたい
It's endless, I want to monopolize your love.
毒だろうが何だろうが抱きしめてあげたい
Whether it's poison or whatever, I want to embrace you.
ライセンス契約 独占のフォーリンラブ
A licensing agreement, an exclusive falling in love.
逃がさないずっと
I'll never let you go, forever.
君が好きってこの感情に騙されてる
I'm being deceived by this feeling of 'I love you.'
大事な方は君か私か決めかねてる
I can't decide who is more important, you or me.
甘すぎる君へ
To you, who are far too sweet.
私興味ないよ君なんて
I have no interest in you at all.
ほら振り回してよ好きなだけ
Go on, lead me around as much as you like.
傲慢で稀重なこの愛は
Because this arrogant and precious love,
渡さないから
I won't hand it over.
馬鹿だよね 色ボケだね それ見たことかださださ
You're a fool, love-blinded, serves you right, so uncool.
もう他でもないあなたに呪われたまま
Still being cursed by none other than you.
いや興味ないよ君なんて
No, I have no interest in you at all.
馬鹿なフリしてあげただけ
I was only pretending to be a fool for you.
愛と愛をぶつけ合って ぐちゃぐちゃになって保存
Let's crash our love against each other and become a jumbled mess.
私興味ないよ君なんて
I have no interest in you at all.
中途半端な容れ物(イレ)で舐めた真似
Making light of me with such a half-hearted vessel.
傲慢で稀重なこの愛に壊されないで
Don't let yourself be destroyed by this arrogant and precious love.
剥がされないで愛保存
Don't let love be torn away.
剥がされないで愛
見た目だけじゃ終わらない 私のこと可愛いと言ったけど
It doesn't end with just looks; you called me cute, but...
まさかそれだけと思っていないよね 私のホント知っていてほしい
...surely you don't think that's all there is to me? I want you to know the real me.
要領良くこなすのがアイデンティティ 不測の事態も動じない
Doing things efficiently is my identity; I never flinch even in unforeseen events.
おすましフェイスでいるけれど 心は常に青白く燃える
Though I keep a composed face, my heart is always burning pale blue.
諦めはしない 媚びたりもしない 私負けない
I won't give up, I won't flatter, and I won't lose.
扱いやすい奴だと思うな 甘く見ると痛い目見るぞ
Don't think of me as someone easy to handle; underestimate me and you'll get hurt.
それでも時には逃げ出してしまいたい
Even so, sometimes I just want to run away.
そんな衝動に襲われ吐き出す夜もある
There are nights when I'm overcome by such urges and let it all out.
ほんの小さな小さな妥協が 積み重なり重なって 動けない
Just a tiny, tiny compromise piling up and up makes me unable to move.
大きな大きな可能性失くし 未来を狭めてしまうから
Because it will lose huge, huge possibilities and narrow down my future.
どんなに苦しくても 辛くても 後悔だけはしない
No matter how painful or bitter, I will never regret.
生き方を見せたいんじゃなくて 生き方なんだ
It's not that I want to show off my way of life, it is my way of life.
現実と理想との距離を縮められなかったとしても
Even if I couldn't shorten the distance between reality and my ideals,
おすましフェイスでいるだけ 何事も無かったかのように
I'll just keep a composed face, as if nothing happened.
立ち止まりはしない 後戻りもしない 夢も捨てない
I won't stop, I won't go back, and I won't throw away my dreams.
私らしく 私らしく
In my own way, in my own way.
勝手なイメージ 決めつけないで 全て私
Don't push your assumptions on me, it's all me.
それでも時には 温もりが恋しい
Even so, sometimes, I long for warmth.
そんな感情に 流されて しまいそうな夜もある
There are nights when I feel like getting swept away by such emotions.
こんな甘い甘い言葉だけ求めてしまうような弱い私じゃない
I'm not so weak that I'd just seek sweet, sweet words.
1回2回 経験だって 私を強くしてくれたから
Because even experiencing it once or twice has made me stronger.
これがこれが私の本当
This, this is the real me.
とても狭い狭い世界の中だけで終わらせるつもりはないんだ
I have no intention of letting it end within such a very narrow world.
広い広い世界の果てまで 駆け抜けていってゆくんだから
Because I'm going to run all the way to the end of this wide, wide world!
どんなに苦しくて傷ついても楽しんでやるさ
No matter how painful or hurtful it is, I'll make sure to enjoy it!
いけてるのも見せてめちゃくちゃじゃなくて生き方なんだから
Showing my cool side, not just being a mess, because it's my way of life!
アナスタシスガール feat. ラプラス・ダークネス
[Anastasis Girl feat. Laplus Darkness]
あれもこれもそれもタブー
This, that, and everything else is taboo.
分かってるの？待ってよ
Do you understand? Wait up.
ノイズ スパイス ぐちぐち 邪魔する
Noise and spice, grumbling and getting in the way.
分かってるの 届いてるでしょ
I understand, you hear me, right?
誰がベスト？ 聞き飽きたペースト
Who's the best? I'm tired of copy-pasted opinions.
手を貸す準備はできた？
Are you ready to lend a hand?
前ならえは蹴り上げるぜ ビクター
I'll kick down the status quo, victor!
脳面上だけを終え 挑発してもね
Even if you finish just on the surface and try to provoke us...
痛いの 痛いの 飛んでいけないくらい
It hurts, it hurts, so much I can't fly away.
勝算 悪化の細胞で 脳内戦 爪出しましょう
With deteriorating cells of potential success, let's fight inside our minds and show our claws.
あたし アナスタシスガール 不滅の強さが手に入る
I'm the Anastasis Girl, gaining immortal strength.
だから nanana... いち、にの、さんで だんだんだん
So, nanana... on the count of three, bam, bam, bam!
アナスタシスガール 昨日いじめたバツ
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying me yesterday.
君は nanana... 地獄へ だんだんだん
You, nanana... straight to hell, down, down, down.
革命御来 革命御来 革命御来 アナスタシスガール
Behold the revolution, behold the revolution, behold the revolution! Anastasis Girl!
お口チャック
Zip your mouth.
耳も離さないつもり
I don't intend to let your ears go.
お口チャック あたしだけに囁け
Zip your mouth, whisper only to me.
健やかなるときも 病めるときも
In sickness and in health.
ずっと人間らしくあれ
Always remain human.
微妙な調節が不可欠
Subtle adjustments are essential.
対応 対応 対応 対応
Response, response, response, response.
痛いの 痛いの 飛んでいけないなら
It hurts, it hurts, if I can't fly away...
やっちゃいな挑戦者 精神論で 目には目をお返しいたしましょう
Go for it, challenger! With willpower, let's return an eye for an eye.
あたし アナスタシスガール ブレイクアウトの時間
I'm the Anastasis Girl, it's time for a breakout.
だから nanana... いち、にの、さんで だんだんだん
So, nanana... on the count of three, bam, bam, bam!
アナスタシスガール 極めて遺憾です
Anastasis Girl, it's extremely regrettable.
君は nanana... 地獄へ だんだんだん
You, nanana... straight to hell, down, down, down.
革命御来 革命御来 革命御来 アナスタシスガール
Behold the revolution, behold the revolution, behold the revolution! Anastasis Girl!
あぁ あぁ お願い放っといて
Ah, ah, please leave me alone.
お度量君の買って その度犠牲にしてる
Catering to your whims, sacrificing myself every time.
汚れるだけの肌 むき出し稼働中
Skin that only gets dirty is exposed and in operation.
あたし アナスタシスガール 不滅の強さが手に入る
I'm the Anastasis Girl, gaining immortal strength.
だから nanana... いち、にの、さんで だんだんだん
So, nanana... on the count of three, bam, bam, bam!
アナスタシスガール 昨日いじめたバツ
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying me yesterday.
君は nanana... 地獄へ だんだんだん
You, nanana... straight to hell, down, down, down.
革命御来 革命御来 革命御来 アナスタシスガール
Behold the revolution, behold the revolution, behold the revolution! Anastasis Girl!
好きじゃない？ 好きじゃない？ あぁ！
Don't you like me? Don't you like me? Ah!
スキデカ！〜スキはデカく回顧録？〜
[Title: Sukideka! ~Love is a Giant Memoir?~]
Loveのレポート 冷めやらぬ感情
My love report, feelings that won't cool down.
馬鹿じゃないの 目を醒まして ねぇ
Aren't you stupid? Wake up, hey!
全然平常心で 興味と過信だらけ
With total composure, full of interest and overconfidence,
さらけ出して Want you
exposing it all, I want you.
チェックアウトできなくて困る
I can't check out, and it's troubling,
でもたまに構ってあげる
but I'll pay attention to you sometimes.
クセになりちまう 絶妙な距離感
It'll become a habit, an exquisite sense of distance.
ゲーム 近く 近付く
Game, close, getting closer.
一生デカく デカく デカく
Forever giant, giant, giant,
何でも頂戴 最大好き作りましょう
give me anything, let's make the biggest love!
それがライクなのかな？ ラブなのかな？ はたまた両方なんでわ！
Is that like? Or is it love? Or is it both, like, what!
なし あり なし あり 絶対あんだろう
No, yes, no, yes, there definitely is!
そしてデカく デカく デカく デカく デカくデカく 夢は全部叶うからね防衛
And giant, giant, giant, giant! Giant, giant, all dreams will come true!
結局 思い描いた タロット占い
In the end, what we envisioned... tarot fortune telling!
一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's do this together!
好きは デカく 好きデカく
Love is giant, love is giant!
縛らなく付き合い よろしくな
Please be with me without tying me down!
たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Deliver many feelings to everyone.
俺だけにみせてくれたって いいな いいな
I hope you show it only to me, wouldn't that be nice?
一人と区別 サービスはできません
No special treatment or services for just one person.
それでもいいかな？ お、ね、が、い
Is that still okay? P-l-e-a-s-e.
もっと知りたいことだらけ
There's still so much more I want to know,
でも知らない方が幸せか
but maybe ignorance is bliss.
絶妙な距離感
An exquisite sense of distance.
ゲーム バランス 取り合う
A game of balancing with each other.
一生つかず離れずは 辛いから
Because being together yet apart is painful...
ちょうどよく按配で お互いもっと分かり合えたら
...let's keep just the right balance. If we could understand each other more...
特別になれる？ いつも通じ合える
...could we become special? We'd always understand each other.
この先は 想像できないけど
Though I can't imagine what lies ahead,
結構いい感じかも ギリギリにでもいいか
it might actually feel pretty good. Even if it's barely there, is it okay?
そのまま進みます 踏みつけて行きます
We'll keep going just like this, we'll trample right through!
今後の我々について話し合っていきたい！ - そんなのいらないでしょ！ - いいからほら！ Three, Two, One, Let's Go!
I want to discuss our future! - We don't need that! - Come on, just do it! Three, Two, One, Let's Go!
一生スレ違うふたり
Two people who always cross paths,
一生デカく デカく デカく デカく
forever giant, giant, giant, giant,
何でも頂戴 最大好き作りましょう
give me anything, let's make the biggest love!
それがライクなのかな？ ラブなのかな？ はたまた両方なんでわ！
Is that like? Or is it love? Or is it both, like, what!
なし あり なし あり 絶対あんだろう
No, yes, no, yes, there definitely is!
そしてデカく デカく デカく デカく デカくデカく 夢は全部叶うからね
And giant, giant, giant, giant! Giant, giant, all dreams will come true!
結局 思い描いた タロット占い
In the end, what we envisioned... tarot fortune telling!
一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's do this together!
一生つかず離れずあきれず ちょうどよく按配で
Forever keeping a distance, never getting tired of each other, in perfect balance.
お前ともっと くだらないことでも 笑っていたい
I want to laugh with you more, even over the silliest things.
付き合っていたい
I want to be with you.
この先も変わらない関係性を
An unchanging relationship even from now on,
不思議な関係 お見知りおきを
please get to know our mysterious relationship!
Private EyeZ
[Song: Private EyeZ]
超常現象フェノメノン 行きつく東奔西走タイムレス
Supernatural phenomenon, running east and west timelessly.
手遅れか？ もう最強か？ 今 焼き付けろ
Is it too late? Or already the strongest? Burn it in now!
超常現象フェノメノン 行きつく東奔西走タイムレス
Supernatural phenomenon, running east and west timelessly.
我らの目で捉えて 煌めいて パン パン パン パン
Catching it with our eyes, sparkling, bang bang bang bang!
満月の夜 くぐり抜けて
Slipping through the night of the full moon,
ベールの隙間まで ため息
a sigh reaching even the gaps in the veil.
もう逃げらんないわ
There's no running away anymore.
変化 カモフラージュ 迷彩 ミリオン
Change, camouflage, disguise, million.
12時ラッシュ 完食チョコレート
12:00 rush, finish off the chocolate.
エトセトラ ダンスフロアを裂くサイレン
Et cetera, the siren tearing through the dance floor.
君のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for you.
闇を燃やしてメラメラ
Burning up the darkness.
どんな時もこの声を届けたい
I want to deliver this voice no matter when.
崖っぷちでメラメラ
Burning on the edge of a cliff.
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up.
恩返し 奇跡のおまじない
A miracle spell to return the favor.
マスター セクト クラス サンキュー
Master, sect, class, thank you.
綺麗な天然記念
A beautiful natural monument.
少女 センセーショナル 意外と生涯だって お真面目
A sensational girl, surprisingly serious for life.
どこにいたって迷子になっちゃってもプンプンです
No matter where I am, even if I get lost, I'll be huffy!
有象無象でも群れ巻いて
Even the rabble gathers in a crowd.
電光石火のエスケープ
A lightning-fast escape!
君のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for you.
愛を燃やしてメラメラ
Burning with love.
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Since that day I swore to protect you.
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for tomorrow.
この波に乗ってセーラー
Ride this wave, sailor!
退屈なんて無縁でしょ？サヨナラ
Boredom is completely irrelevant, right? Goodbye!
超常現象フェノメノン
Paranormal phenomenon,
東奔西走タイムレフト
running east and west, time left,
今焼き付けろ
burn it into your memory now!
超常現象フェノメノン
Paranormal phenomenon,
東奔西走タイムレフト
running east and west, time left,
胸のメラメラ
the fire in my chest,
夢のメラメラ
the fire of my dreams,
バ・バ・バ・バ・バ・バ
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
ねー！ねー！ねー！ねー！るーちゃん！めっちゃ良かったね！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Lui-chan! That was so good!
めっちゃ良かったね！ねー！めっちゃ楽しかったね！
It was so great! Right?! That was super fun!
マジかっこいい！あ、これめっちゃ良いよね！
So cool! Oh, this is really nice!
まだ終わってないから、まだ終わってないよ！そっかそっか、これからは最高だよね！
We're not done yet, we're not done yet! Right, right, from here on is the best part!
何これ？何これ？お？お？あ！
What is this? What is this? Oh? Oh? Ah!
あ、気づいちゃいました？
Ah, did you notice?
何これ、変なのばかりだ / 変なの
What's this? It's weird. / How weird.
変じゃない、めっちゃかっこいいじゃん！こよが作りました！
It's not weird, it's super cool! Koyo made this!
また！また経費使ったんか！
Again?! Did you use the company budget again?!
これがござるの給料からカット...
This gets deducted from Gozaru's salary...
いやいやいやいや！ござるの給料からだろうが何だろうが給料は同じだから！
No, no, no! No matter where it's deducted from, my salary is still the same!
ごまかしてんな！
You're dodging the question!
ということで、これは告知用カードを、もうめくっちゃう？
And so, these are cards for announcements! Shall we flip one already?
お、早い！何これ？告知！
Oh, so fast! What's this? An announcement!
ということで、この流れでね、グッズ紹介でございますね！
So, following that, we have our merchandise reveal!
今回はそういう感じね！いいんじゃん！
So that's how it is this time! Sounds good!
はい、じゃあ私からね、行きますよ！
Alright, I'll start us off!
はい、ホロックス活動、もうどこ見ればいいかわかんない！
Okay, holoX's activity... I don't even know which camera to look at!
ホロックス活動4周年記念グッズ！Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade、今日の18時より販売開始されております！
holoX 4th Anniversary Commemorative Merch! Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade is now on sale starting from 6:00 PM today!
それでは、それぞれ見ていきましょう！まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙、ドン！
Now, let's take a look at each item! First up, the Premium Acrylic Art Board, bam!
今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です！
This is an acrylic art board featuring our new key visual!
なんと、複製サインとロゴが箔押しになってて、めっちゃいい感じ！
And the printed autographs and logo are foil-stamped, making it look amazing!
かっこいい！かっこいい！
So cool! It looks great!
そしてお次がこちら、ホロカスリーブ！
And next up is this, holoX Sleeves!
このカードが、まさにそれなんですけど...
These cards are exactly that...
キービジュアルを使ったホロカスリーブです！こちらなんと60枚入り！
These are card sleeves featuring our key visual! They come in a pack of 60!
わお！やったねみんな！
Wow! We did it, everyone!
何枚買ってもいいですからね！使いやすいですしね！
You can buy as many as you want! They're very easy to use!
そして、アクリルスタンド！
And next, Acrylic Stands!
おー！めちゃかっこいい！我々、やってます
Oh! So cool! Look at us go!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいね！
They have different facial expressions than the key visual, so please compare them with the art board!
気持ち悪っ / 帰りまーす / 帰ってきた、帰ってきた
Gross... / We're leaving. / They came back, they came back.
こよと、いろはも可愛いね！
Koyori and Iroha look cute too!
可愛い！
So cute!
そして、こちら！記念メダルも発売しております！
And next, Commemorative Medals are also on sale!
なんとね、ケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます！
These commemorative medals actually come with a case and a pouch!
こちら、期生ごとでデザインが異なっておりますので...
Since the designs vary for each generation...
なんと今回はホロックスだけのデザインになっております！ぜひぜひゲットしてよくチェックしてみてください！
This time, they feature a design exclusive to holoX! Be sure to get yours and check it out!
なんか騒がしいな... そのドリルやめろ、そのドリルやめろ
It's getting noisy... Stop that drill, stop that drill!
はい、ということで、次は何のカードにしようかな？カード、ドーン！オープン！
Alright, so which card should we choose next? Card, bam! Open!
あるのね
There's more?
ということで、タイミ―コラボ！
And so, a collaboration with Timee!
やってましたね！
We did that!
以前タイミ―で募集したレアバイトなんですけど、現地の様子があるということで、見てみましょう！ドン！
We previously recruited for a rare part-time job on Timee. We have footage from the site, so let's check it out! Bam!
おー！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
ホロックスのコスプレしてる！ホロックスのコスしてる！
They're cosplaying as holoX! They are cosplaying holoX!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you, everyone!
他もありますよ、ドン！
There's more, bam!
配ってる！
They're handing things out!
めっちゃ配られてる、めっちゃ見られてる！なんだあれ
They're handing out so many, and getting stared at! What's that?
なるようになる！
It'll work out!
でもこれで知ってくれた人もいるよね、たぶん。
But there are probably people who came to know us through this, right?
ねえ！絶対そう！
Yeah! Absolutely!
もう1枚やります、トーン！
Let's do one more. Bam!
おお！え、待って、新宿？
Oh! Wait, Shinjuku?
あれ、後ろも写ってる？あれ聞いてた？
Wait, is that us in the back too? Did we hear about that?
聞いてないよ！
I didn't hear about that!
待って、今日のあの21時前に流れていたあのよくわからない...
Wait, that mysterious video playing before 21:00 today...
あのよくわからない... おい、流れてたのかよ！大丈夫か？
That mysterious... Hey, was it playing?! Is it okay?
でも、もっとさ、なんかかっこいいMVとかさ、ライブ映像とか流したらもっと...
But if they played a cooler MV or live concert footage, it would be...
どういうこと？どういうこと？
What do you mean? What do you mean?
いや、でもありがとう！ありがとう！
No, but thank you! Thank you!
ということで、こちら、応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
So, how many applications do you think we got for this?
でもさ、お仕事だからね。お仕事だからやっぱり...
But you know, it's a workday. Since it's work, after all...
100人とか来てくれてる？
Maybe like 100 people came?
そう、大変だからね。
Yeah, it's tough, right?
なんと！数千人の応募が来ているということです！
Incredibly, we received several thousand applications!
ええええ？！すごすぎる！
Whaaaat?! That's amazing!
うれしい！ありがとう！驚きすぎ、驚きすぎ。
So happy! Thank you! Surprised too much, surprised too much.
給料もらったからって...
Just because we got paid...
給料もらったからって、決まってるわけじゃない...
Just because we got paid, it doesn't mean...
あの、いろはより多めに渡してます。
We paid her more than Iroha.
ちょっとやめて、福利厚生、タイムイさんですからね。
Stop that. Welfare program, it's thanks to Timee-san.
タイムイさん、ありがとうございます。そして、応募してくれた19人のみんなもありがとうございます。
Thank you very much, Timee-san. And thank you to the 19 people who applied too.
そして、次はなんだ？おお！オープン！
And what's next? Oh! Open!
来い来い来い！何これ？お、来た！じゃじゃーん！タワーコラボだ！
Come on, come on! What is this? Oh, here it is! Ta-da! It's a tower collaboration!
タワー！
Tower!
ということで、皆さんタワーコラボ、もう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
So, everyone, the information for the tower collaboration has already been released, but here it is!
全国4カ所で行われる、holoXタワーインベージョン！
The holoX Tower Invasion, held at four locations nationwide!
12月4日から開催されます！札幌テレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力ミライタワー、梅田スカイビルで開催されますので、ぜひ、皆さん行ってくださいね！
It will be held starting December 4th! It will take place at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER, and Umeda Sky Building, so please go visit, everyone!
行ってねー！俺たちが、俺たちがタワーです！
Please go! We are... We are the towers!
おい、おい！今回大事なことがあるんですけど、ちゃんと予約しておかないとですね、皆さん入れないんで。事前予約必須です！
Hey, hey! There's an important thing this time: if you don't make a reservation properly, you won't be able to get in. Advance reservations are mandatory!
そう、そうなんです。事前予約忘れてる人も多分いると思うので。
Yes, that's right. Some people might have forgotten to make an advance reservation.
その場で行っても入れないらしいです。
Apparently, you can't enter even if you go there in person.
そう、予約を忘れずに！
Yes, don't forget to reserve!
事前予約よろしくお願いします！
Please make your advance reservations!
しとかないと、しとかないと。はい、お次！オープン！
Gotta do it, gotta do it. Okay, next! Open!
はい！なんと、なんと！ホロライブの新サービス、新しいサービス、ライブの感動を最速でお届け！
Yes! Unbelievably! Hololive's new service, a new service to deliver the excitement of the live concert at the fastest speed!
おお、すごい！どういうこと？
Oh, amazing! What does that mean?
秘密結社holoX、4周年のライブブロマイドが、なんと！今日のライブの写真が、明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだ！
The Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary Live Bromide, incredibly! The photos from today's concert can be printed out at convenience stores starting tomorrow!
えええ！手に入るんだ！すごーい！対象店舗は、ファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります！
Whaaat! You can get them! That's awesome! The target stores are FamilyMart, Lawson, and Ministop!
イェーイ！ありがとうございます！いっぱいある！
Yay! Thank you very much! There are so many!
そして、今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです。
And apparently, you can purchase them online starting now.
マジで？！
Really?!
ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので、詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
However, starting tomorrow, it seems you can also purchase them while choosing the photos at convenience stores. For details, please check the link in the bottom left!
こっちこっちこっち！
Over here, over here!
さらにですね、今回は、そちらのお写真に、ブロマイドに、私達のメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけど...
Furthermore, this time, it seems we can add our messages to those photos, to the bromides...
えええ！すごい！
Wow! Amazing!
今から書く。今から書く？
We're writing them now. Writing them now?
え、ちょっと待って！ここで書くの？！
Wait a minute! We're writing them here?!
考えて、書いてください。
Think about it, and please write.
はい！え、はい...
Yes! Wait, yes...
ちょっと待って、何書こう...
Wait a minute, what should I write...
時間も迫ってますから、早く書いてくださいね。
Time is running out, so please write quickly.
意外と集中力使う。
This actually takes a lot of concentration.
よし、書けた！
Alright, I wrote it!
書けた？見せて！
Did you write it? Let me see!
これ、かわいい。ぽい、ぽい。こよっぽい。
This is cute. It looks like it. Very Koyo-like.
こよっぽい。みんな書けた？書いて、書いて。みんな出して。はい、お願いしますね。ということで、これでお願いします。
Koyo-like. Did everyone write it? Write it, write it. Show it. Yes, please. So, we'll go with this.
みんな何書いたかすごく気になると思うんですが、こちらのメッセージの内容は、みんなが...
I'm sure everyone is very curious about what we wrote, but the content of these messages, everyone...
あの、私が書いた...
Um, what I wrote...
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ！言っちゃダメ！
No, no, no! Don't say it!
ダメに決まってんだろ！サプライズだから！
Of course not! It's a surprise!
あ、ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい。
Ah, sorry, sorry.
はい、そして、まだ2枚あるんで。お次はこちら！
Yes, and we still have two cards. Next is this!
オープン！なんと！あの作品とコラボ！？
Open! Unbelievably! A collaboration with *that* work!?
え？！何、何？あの作品ってどれ？
What?! What, what? Which work is "that" work?
ちょっと待って、これはマジで知らない。どれだ？あの作品って何ですか？
Wait a minute, I seriously don't know this one. Which is it? What is "that work"?
こちらをどうぞ！
Here you go!
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That mysterious group...
偶像――“アキドル”
ナノダト云フ。
...is said to be idols ("akidoru").
ソシテ――
And...
正確ナ話ヲスルト、
征服ショウトシテイルノハ
エデンノ星ノラシイ。
To be precise, it seems they are
trying to conquer the planet Eden.
タダ、ドウイウコトカ、
交ハルハズノナキ世界ガ、
今回バカリハ
油断シテシマッタラシイ。
However, somehow, the worlds that were never
supposed to cross have let their guard down.
交
kou. (2021)
Cross
秘密結社holoX × 物語シリーズ 其ノ零
Secret Society holoX x Monogatari Series: Part Zero
〈物語〉シリーズ × holoX
コラボ開催決定！
"Monogatari Series" x holoX
Collaboration Confirmed!
ええーー！？うそ！
いいの！？え、やばい！
What!? No way!
Is this allowed!? Oh my god!
え、やば！やばすぎる！
Wait, crazy! This is insane!
え、めちゃめちゃ大好きじゃん、ね！
ね、好き！
Wait, we love this series so much, don't we!
Yeah, we love it!
え、やばすぎる！どういうこと！？
え、どこか行っちゃった！
This is too crazy! What does this mean!?
Wait, it went away!
ええーー！
What! No way!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
なんと！マジで！？
え、怒られない？吾輩。
Look at that! Seriously!?
Wait, won't I get scolded?
怒られない、怒られない！
怒られたら大々的に出てないから！
You won't get scolded!
If we were, this wouldn't be featured so prominently!
早く言って！早く言って！
なんと『〈物語〉シリーズ』との...
Tell us sooner! Tell us sooner!
Actually, our collaboration with...
コラボが決定しました！
どういうこと！？
the "Monogatari Series" has been confirmed!
What does this mean!?
って皆も言ってる！詳細は随時発表されるようなので、お楽しみに！
That's what everyone is saying!
Details will be announced gradually, so stay tuned!
え、我々も分かっていない。
Wait, even we don't know the details.
そうなんです。本当に詳細が何も分かっていないんですよ。
That's right. We really don't know any details yet.
知らないんですか？
え、どうなんでしょうか？
You really don't know?
Well, I wonder...
いやちょっと、我々も動揺してるんですけれども、
Honestly, we're a bit shaken too, but...
え、いいんですか？本当に？
という感じなんですけれど...
"Is this really okay?"
That's how we feel...
なんと最後に一つ！
But wait, we have one last thing!
あるみたいなので、そちらをいきましょう！
もう一個見ないといけないので、一旦動揺を落ち着かせて、
It seems we have one more thing, let's check it out!
We have to look at another one, so let's calm down...
みんな落ち着いて！私たちが動揺している間に、
Everyone calm down! While we are panicking,
皆さんこの6つ目が何か、
コメントで教えてみてください！
everyone, try guessing what this sixth one is
in the comments!
何かな？予想してみて。
コメント見に行こう。
What is it? Guess it.
Let's check the comments.
何があるかな？
シノブ？シノブじゃない？
What could it be?
Shinobu? Is it Shinobu?
え、何？なんでコソコソしてるの？
Wait, what? Why are you whispering?
最後の1つは皆さん何だと思いますか？
What do you all think the last one is?
なんとですね、まあちょっとヒントを言うと、
今年新曲作りましたよね。
Actually, to give you a little hint,
we made new songs this year, right?
いっぱい出た！
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
We released so many!
In total, how many songs does holoX have?
何曲だ？こよし！
How many? Koyori!
え、たくさん！
覚えてないのか？
Uh, a lot!
Do you not remember?!
holoXが今まで出してきた、企画を除きますと、
Excluding special projects,
all the songs holoX has released...
全部で7曲あります！
total 7 songs!
ってことは？
Which means...?
もしや？
みんな分かってきたんじゃない？
Could it be...?
I think everyone's starting to realize!
あ、分かってる、分かってる！ということで、
気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、
Oh, they know, they know!
It seems some people have already figured it out,
やっぱりあちらでございます！
6枚目、オープン！
so yes, it is indeed that!
Sixth card, open!
ちゃん！なんとファーストアルバムが出ます！
Ta-da! Our first album is coming out!
やったー！嬉しい！
Yay! I'm so happy!
ということで、ファーストアルバム、ファーストオーダー、
じゃない、ファーストアルバム『Secret ORDER』！
And so, our first album... "First Order"...
wait, no! Our first album "Secret ORDER"!
間違えた、間違えた。シークレットオーダーだよ！
I made a mistake, I made a mistake.
It's "Secret ORDER"!
こちらだよ！
Here it is!
はい、こちらの『Secret ORDER』、holoXでの4年間をギュッと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
Yes, this "Secret ORDER" is an album packed with
our four years in holoX!
我々のデビュー曲『JOYAry Paint』はオリジナルバージョンに加えて、本作のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
In addition to the original version of our debut song
"JOYAry Paint", a newly rearranged version created
specifically for this album is also included!
そして、さらに、なんかまだ未発表の楽曲も！？
And furthermore, there are also some unreleased songs!?
え、何曲入ってるってこと！？
8曲とか、9曲、10曲、11曲とか！？
Wait, how many songs are in there!?
Like 8, 9, 10, or 11 songs!?
多すぎる、多すぎる！
That's way too many!
ということでですね、通常盤になるんですけれども、
あ、ちょっと、上が見えないです。
And so, here is the regular edition, but...
ah, I can't see the top of the screen.
早い早い、流れがね。すみません。通常盤には初回限定特典があります！
It's moving too fast. Sorry.
The regular edition comes with a first-press bonus!
こちらでございますね。
Here it is.
各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット4種類のうち、ランダムで1枚つきます。
You will get one random jacket featuring
a solo version of a member out of four designs.
そして、こちらですね、4枚並べると、どうやら1枚絵になるとのことですよ！
And look at this!
If you line up all four, they form a single illustration!
え、すごい！すごい嬉しそうな顔してる！
Wow, amazing! They look so happy!
ラプラスちゃんの角が、刀の上に...本当だ！並べたい！
La+-chan's horn is right on top of the sword...
Oh, it's true! I want to line them up!
並べないと！
We have to!
そして、完全生産限定盤封入特典は、かっこよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが！？
And for the complete limited edition bonus,
this cool album features a secret gimmick very fitting for holoX!?
秘密の仕掛け？え、我々も分かってないぞ。
A secret gimmick?
Wait, even we don't know about it.
隠されているとか。何だって？
はい、ちょっと私たちも分からないのですが、衣
Like, something is hidden. What is it?
Well, we don't really know either, but...
この後22時から販売開始です！
sales start right after this at 22:00!
是非是非ご予約お願いいたします！
Please make sure to pre-order yours!
ということで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけど、
はい、この告知カードちゃんたちはこれで役目も終わりよ。バイバーイ！
So, we had tons of announcements,
but now these announcement cards have served
their purpose. Bye-bye!
こよー！このギミックやばいだろ。
これで消せんの？
Koyo! This gimmick is crazy.
Can you erase them with this?
それだけね。
Just that!
ということで、ライブもラストパートでございます。
And so, we are now entering the final part of our live show.
この後ですね、何やら、ちょっと、
お知らせ？サプライズ？があるらしいですよ！
After this, it seems there's some kind of...
announcement? Or surprise!?
はい、最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いいたします！
Yes, please keep your eyes glued to the channel
until the very end!
みんな、最後まで楽しんでいくぞ！
Everyone, let's have fun until the end!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
こうべを垂れよ！
Bow your heads!
イエス、マイ・ダーク！
Yes, My Dark!
一刀両断！叩き切る！
Cleaving in twain! Cut them down!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ！
You children wandering in the endless cycle of rebirth!
漆黒の翼で誘おう
I shall invite you with pitch-black wings.
我ら、エデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社...
We are the rulers of the Star of Eden, the Secret Society...
holoX！
holoX!
いざ参るでござる！
Here we come!
Whoa oh, Whoa oh oh oh oh...
反乱？どうしようもないこの世界
Rebellion? There's nothing to be done about this world.
壊してほしい？
Do you want it destroyed?
ならば...
If so...
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell tolling the end is ringing.
パパパパタバタ Every single night
Pa-pa-pa-pa-tabata Every single night
陰キャも陽キャも Sing a song loud！
In-kyas and You-kyas alike, Sing a song loud!
気持ち良いことだけがすべて 落ちていく 闇の底へ
Only feeling good is everything, falling to the bottom of the darkness.
甘い甘いメロディ ほら どうぞ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
A sweet, sweet melody, come on, this way, this way, towards the clapping hands.
もう人間でいられない
You can't be human anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば...
Come on, if you dye yourself in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ！
Repaint the world!
望めば呉れてやろう 全て
If you wish, I will give you everything.
常識を破り捨てろ！
Tear up common sense!
狂う 狂う 狂い倒せ 火を付けろ！
Go crazy, crazy, lose your mind! Set it on fire!
Wow wow wow wow...
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Eat up everything.
Wow wow wow wow...
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Whoa oh, Whoa oh oh oh oh...
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ ついてきな
正義とか知らない 地ならしして誘い
The charisma of evil, I will guide you, follow me
I don't know about justice, leveling the ground and inviting you
真面目に不真面目 天才の通常運転
望み求め 願い叶える 世界征服！
Seriously unserious, the genius's normal operation
Seeking desires, granting wishes, world conquest!
パパパパタバタ Every single night
Pa-pa-pa-pa-tabata Every single night
退屈な世界へ バイバイバイ
Bye-bye to the boring world.
醒めることのない夢を見せる
I will show you a dream you won't wake up from.
ほら お眠りなさい
Come, please go to sleep.
もっともっと遠くへ ほら どうぞ どうぞ 行きたいんでしょう...
Further and further, come on, this way, this way, you want to go, don't you?
もう止められない
You can't stop anymore.
ほら 悪に染まれば...
Come on, if you dye yourself in evil...
世界を塗り替えろ！
Repaint the world!
望む物 与えよう 全て
I will give you everything you want.
ルールを書き換えろ！
Rewrite the rules!
狂う 狂う 掻き回せ 狂い尽くせ
Crazy, crazy, stir it up, go completely crazy!
Wow wow wow wow...
すべての災いものへ
To all calamitous things.
Wow wow wow wow...
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
ついに4周年！ 狂気の宴の始まりだ！
Finally, the 4th anniversary! The banquet of madness begins!
貴様ら、準備はいいか！ 刮目せよ！
Are you bastards ready?! Open your eyes and watch!
holoX！holoX！ 手を上げろ！手を上げろ！
holoX! holoX! Put your hands up! Put your hands up!
叫ぶでござる！
I shall shout!
こより！こより！
Koyori! Koyori!
踊って！踊って！
Dance! Dance!
世界を征服する holoX！世界を変えていく holoX！
holoX conquers the world! holoX changes the world!
ルイ姉！ルイ姉！
Lui-nee! Lui-nee!
もっと！もっと！
More! More!
ラプラス！ラプラス！
Laplus! Laplus!
最後は全員でいくぞ！
Finally, let's go all together!
holoX！holoX！ 世界を征服する holoX！
世界を変えていく holoX！世界はこの手で holoX！
holoX! holoX! holoX conquers the world!
holoX changes the world! The world is in our hands, holoX!
心を解き放って...
Release your heart.
ほら どうぞ どうぞ 身を任せて
Come, this way, this way, surrender yourself.
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば...
Come on, if you dye yourself in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ！
Repaint the world!
望めば呉れてやろう 全て
If you wish, I will give you everything.
常識を破り捨てろ！
Tear up common sense!
狂う 狂う 狂い倒せ 火を付けろ！
Go crazy, crazy, lose your mind! Set it on fire!
Wow wow wow wow...
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Eat up everything.
Wow wow wow wow...
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Whoa oh, Whoa oh oh oh oh......
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社･･･
We are the rulers of Eden's planet, Secret Society...
ホロックス！いざ、ご参る！
holoX! Let's go!
機は熟した
The time is ripe!
暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ、準備はいいか！
Heroic spirits who have appeared from the dawn darkness, are you ready?!
おーー！！
Ohhh!!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
The night deepens, look, darkness
能ある鷹はPONで隠す
A wise hawk hides its claws... with PON!
脳に従えエゴイスティン
Follow your brain, Egoistin
のっと！にんにん！サムライガール
Not! Nin-nin! Samurai Girl
闇金じゃないけど
It's not loan sharking, but...
フルベッドでしょ...
it's a full bet, right?
征服すればあーけい！
If we conquer it, A-K!
切り裂く赤字
Slicing through deficits...
ジャキンジャキン！
Clink, clank!
悪の手のひら
On the palm of evil...
踊りたくなる
making you want to dance
ほら君も気づけばノリノリです
Look, before you know it, you're grooving too!
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine
It's hopeless, Don't show, No mine
堕ちてく運命
A falling fate
ならしょうがない
So it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
Ex and Ex and Ex and Ex...
交差する真ん中で
at the center where they intersect
ネクストとネクストとネクストとネクストと
Next and Next and Next and Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
the world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
飛び乗れ 飛び乗れ 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Jump on, jump on, towards where the darkness calls
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
暗黒の 暁闇エクスデス
Dark dawn, Exdesu
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！皆のもの、かかれ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world into the colors of holoX! Everyone, charge!
Yes My Dark!!!
完璧漆黒∞（アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ）、エデンの星は我が手中に！
Absolute Darkness Infinity! The planet Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホークアイ！ お前もholoXerの一員となるのだ！
Evil Eye, Hawkeye! You too shall become a member of the holoXers!
コヨニウムボンバー！これで君もコヨにメロメロ～！
Koyonium Bomber! Now you'll fall head over heels for Koyo!
疾風木枯らし斬り！一刀両断叩き斬る！
Gale Dry-Wind Slash! Slicing them cleanly in two!
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine
It's hopeless, Don't show, No mine
堕ちてく運命
A falling fate
ならしょうがない
So it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now
刮目せよ！
Feast your eyes!
エクスとエクスとエクスとエクスが
Ex and Ex and Ex and Ex...
交差する真ん中で
at the center where they intersect
ネクストとネクストとネクストとネクストと
Next and Next and Next and Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
the world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
媚びるな [complete zero] つまり最＆高...
Don't flatter (complete zero), in other words, the absolute best!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
笑うのは holoXです
The ones who laugh will be holoX!
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappappa LaPaLaPa Rappappa
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa Rappappa
Yeah!!!
[秘密結社holoXより一件の通知]
[One notification from Secret Society holoX]
[SECRET ORDER]
[機ハ熟シター]
[The time is ripe—]
[全テノ "holoXer" ヘ告グー]
[To all "holoXers"—]
[集へ、決戦ノ地ー]
[Gather, at the land of the final battle—]
[2026.4.29]
[PIA ARENA MM]
[秘密結社holoX Live 2026 "1st MISSION"]
[Secret Society holoX Live 2026 "1st MISSION"]
[世界ヲ手ニスル準備ハイイカ]
[Are you ready to take over the world?]
[狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ]
[The banquet of madness begins.]
[#SSholoX世界リペイント計画]
[#SSholoXWorldRepaintProject]
やったーー！！！
We did it!!!
やったよ！ / ついにやった！
We did it! / We finally did it!
やったね！ / いやー緊張した！
We did indeed! / Man, that was nerve-wracking!
みんなも盛り上がってくれてたね！
Everyone was really getting into it!
みんな踊ってくれてる？
Is everyone dancing along?
いかがでしたでしょうかー！
How did you all like it?!
はい！やった、やばいね(笑)
Yes! We did it, that was crazy (laughs)
早いよ！まだ早いからね！
Too fast! It's still too early [to wrap up]!
やばいね(笑) / やばいね(笑)
That's crazy! / Yeah, crazy!
やばいね(笑)
Crazy indeed.
ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりましたー！
And so, amazingly, our in-person live concert has been decided!
やったーー！！！ / ありがとうございます！
Yay!!! / Thank you so much!
ファーストミッションだよ！
It's our First Mission!
ありがとうございます！早い！
Thank you so much! So fast!
ということで、みんなそれぞれね、感想と、ライブに向けての抱負をお願いしたいと思います！
So, we'd like each of you to share your thoughts and aspirations for the live concert!
まずは、じゃあ、私から。 はい！
First off, let's start with me! / Yes!
ふぅ。はい。
Phew, okay.
決まったな。 決まったね。
We did it! / Yes, we did!
It's decided. / It sure is.
いや、めちゃくちゃね、あの、デビューの時から、ライブやりたいねって、
You know, from the very beginning of our debut, we kept saying we wanted to do a live show,
言ってて、デビュー前から。それが、もうありがたいことにね...
even before our debut. And that has, thankfully...
泣いてる？ 早いよ！
Are you crying? / That's too fast!
みんなの協力のおかげで、ホロッカーさんたちの応援のおかげで、
Thanks to everyone's cooperation, and the support of all the HoloXers,
叶いました！やったー！ ありがとうございます！
it has come true! We did it! / Thank you so much!
えー、もう、ホロックスの、みんなで、当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので、
And now, with all of us in holoX, we want to pump up the venue on that day,
ぜひみんな遊びに来てください！かっこいいホロックスを見に来てね！
so please come and see us! Come see a cool holoX!
見に来てね！ はい、ということで、
Come see us! / Alright, so with that...
続いてはじゃあ、こよ。 はい！
...next is, Koyo. / Yes!
はい！えー、今言ってた通り、みんなライブやりたいねって話もしてたし、
Yes! As she just said, we've all been talking about wanting to do a live show,
やっぱりこよは、一番忘れられない風景が、初めてのフェスで、ホロックスで、
and for Koyo, the most unforgettable scene was our first Fes, when holoX...
やった時の、あの「常夜リペイント」で会場がもうわーってなってくれたのを浴びた時。
...performed "Joya Repaint" and bathed in the crowd going wild.
あれを、もうずっと忘れられないんで、やっぱり、その、今度はね、
I can never forget that, so next time,
ホロッカーさんたちだけの、会場、俺たちの会場で、やれるわけじゃないですか。
we get to do it in a venue filled with only HoloXers—our own venue!
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！そして、できて、本当に、この、
I am incredibly happy! And for making this a reality,
やらせてくれることにしてくれた大人の皆さんにも、ありがとうございます！
I'm really grateful to all the staff who made this possible! Thank you!
この4人の、できる力をすべて出して、そして歌とダンスもね、より一層、力を込めて、
We'll give it everything we've got, putting even more energy into our singing and dancing,
やっていきますので、絶対現地、そして現地来れない人は映像でも絶対見に来てください！
so please come to the venue, and if you can't make it, be sure to watch the stream!
お願いします！ はい、ござる。
Please support us! / Okay, Gozaru.
はい！みんな！生でござるたちの声が聞ける機会、
Yes! Everyone! This is an opportunity to hear our voices live,
ホロックスの、このハーモニーが聞ける機会！ ハーモニー、ハーモニー。
and an opportunity to hear holoX's harmony! / Harmony, harmony.
ハーモニーは無いけど。 地声、俺たちの共鳴、共鳴が聞ける機会！来たぞ！
We don't really have harmony though. / Our speaking voices! An opportunity to hear our resonance! It's here!
いやもう本当にね、ホロックス、やっぱ、本当にみんな言ってるけどデビュー前からね、
Seriously, just like everyone said, we've wanted to do a live show at a venue since before our debut,
このメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので、
with this particular group of members, we've always said we wanted to do it,
それがやっと叶ってね、デカい声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのをね、
so now that it's finally coming true, being able to shout out loud and get hyped together,
今か今かとね、楽しみにしております。我々もね、4人とも、しっかり当日までレッスンや、
I'm eagerly looking forward to it. All four of us will work hard until the day of the concert, doing lessons...
もうね、練習も含めパフォーマンスも全部いろいろみんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて挑みますので、
...and practice, while thinking of lots of things to make the performance enjoyable for you, so...
見ている皆さんもぜひ！全力で楽しみにして、そして当日は楽しんでください！
everyone watching, please look forward to it with all your heart, and have fun on that day!
頑張ります！盛り上げる準備、できてます！ できてるぞー！
We'll do our best! We're ready to pump things up! / We're ready!
はい、最後、総帥、総帥決めてくれ！ お願いしますよ。
Okay, lastly, leader! Leader, wrap it up! / We're counting on you.
毎回この最後やめてほしいんだよな。 しゃーない、しゃーない。
I wish they'd stop putting me last every time. / Can't be helped, can't be helped.
ちょ、みんな、ついに、ホロックスが、俺たちが、
W-well, everyone, finally, holoX—meaning us—
ライブ！！ ライブ、ライブ！
...is doing a live show!! / Live! Live!
もうみんなはさ、もうすごいライブやりたい、音楽大好きみたいな、ずっと聞いてたからさ、
I've always heard everyone saying how much they want to do a live show and how much they love music, so...
俺は嬉しいよ。 いや、もちろん当事者だよ、当事者。
...I'm really happy. / Wait, you're one of the members, you know?
あの、やっぱりライブがね、一番楽しいから、みんなとやってる、
I mean, live shows are the most fun of all, doing it with everyone...
やっぱホロックスの活動の中で、なんかライブって感じじゃん、
In holoX's activities, it really feels like "this is a live show," right?
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロッカーがばーっているところでできるのが嬉しいよな、ラプラス。
So I'm glad we can do that on our own, and especially in front of a huge crowd of HoloXers, right?
嬉しい。俺たち本当に色々あったけど、
I'm glad. We've really been through a lot, but...
これからも本当に、4人いれば大丈夫だから、頑張ろう。
from now on, as long as there are four of us, we'll be fine, so let's do our best.
頑張ろう！ 一致団結していこう！ 頑張るぞ！
Let's do our best! / Let's unite! / We'll do our best!
ありがとう！ 速報です！トレンド1位ということで！
Thank you! / Breaking news! We're trending #1!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ここから4月29日まで、もう止まらねえので、トレンドに入れまくっててください。
From now until April 29th, we won't stop, so please keep tweeting with the hashtag!
はい、ということで改めて、秘密結社holoX ファーストライブ「ファーストミッション」は、
Yes, so once again, Secret Society holoX 1st Live "First Mission"...
4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
...will be held on April 29th at Pia Arena MM!
空けとけよ、空けとけよ！
Keep your calendar open! Open!
もろもろの詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので、皆さん、続報をお待ちください！
Further details will be announced at a later date, so please look forward to more updates!
よろしく、よろしくお願いします！ そして、そして、そして！先ほど聴いていただきました新曲、「共鳴X」です！
Please look forward to it! / And, and, and! The new song you just listened to is "Kyomei X"!
はい、聴いていただきましたけれども、この後、
Yes, we hope you enjoyed it, and after this...
22時10分よりですね、MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
We will premiere the music video at 22:10!
イェーイ！お！
Yay! Oh!
エクスラズ、いいアレですね。かっこいい。そして...
Exlas! That's cool. Nice. And...
本日24時ですね、12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので...
The digital release starts today at 24:00, which is December 2nd at 0:00...
ライブに向けてたくさん聴いてくれよな！
Make sure to listen to it a lot in preparation for the live concert!
いや、もうコールできるとこいっぱいだからね！
Yeah, there are lots of parts where you can do call-and-response!
めちゃめちゃ！もうライブのために...
So much! It's totally for the live...
エクスラズ！エクスラズ！エクスラズ！お前ら新曲聴いて！
Exlas! Exlas! Exlas! Everyone, listen to the new song!
新曲いっぱい聴いて！予習して！
Listen to the new song a lot! Prepare yourself!
ライブ楽しみにして待っててほしい！
And please look forward to the live concert!
そして、アルバム『シークレット・オーダー』を持って！
And, hold your copy of the album "Secret Order"!
持って？持って？奪われないように気をつけてね、持って！
Hold it? Hold it? Be careful not to get it stolen, hold it!
奪われないように？ライブ来てね！
Not stolen? Come to the live!
配らなきゃ！持ってね！
We have to distribute it! Hold it!
聴いて予習してね！アルバムは、えっと...
Listen and prepare! The album is, uh...
22時から販売開始！
...going on sale starting at 22:00!
もう1分ないよ！みんな買ってね！
There's less than a minute left! Everyone, please buy it!
ホロックスのみんな！
Everyone in holoX!
本当に...4周年ありがとう！
Really... thank you for the 4th anniversary!
お祝いしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating with us!
来年は、もうホロックスの、我々の年にしていくので、頑張ろうね！
Next year, we will make it holoX's, our year, so let's do our best!
5年目もよろしくお願いします！
Please support us in our 5th year as well!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
じゃ、みんな、せーので行くよ。せーの...
Now everyone, let's go on three. One, two...
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
バイバイ！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!